A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, China Medical Board records, RG 4 FA114
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1913-1929; 1
  - Appropriations - Alphabetical, 1919-1929; 2
    - H. E. Bard, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 695)
    - Joseph Barlee, 1925-27 (Box 33, Folder 696)
    - M. E. Barnes, 1921-22 (Box 34, Folder 697)
    - Sarah Barnes, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 698)
    - Barnes Hospital, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 699)
    - Robert A. Bartlett, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 700)
    - Mary Beard, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 701)
    - Belgian Mission Institute, 1926 (Box 34, Folder 702)
    - Bellevue Hospital, 1919-26 (Box 34, Folder 703)
    - Beloit College, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 704)
    - Bender Hygienic Laboratory, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 705)
    - Benedictine Medical School, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 706)
    - N. Bercovitz, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 707)
    - Arthur Bevan, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 708)
    - Biological Service Bureau, 1923-27 (Box 34, Folder 709)
      Man to organize purchase of lab animals necessary for the medical schools.
    - Biological Service Bureau, 1923-27 (Box 34, Folder 710)
    - Biological Service Bureau, 1923-27 (Box 34, Folder 711)
    - H. E. Blanco, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 712)
    - J. R. Bloodgood, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 713)
    - Board of Missionary Preparation, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 714)
    - Arlie Bock, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 715)
    - Ernest Bogart, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 716)
    - Bonding of Officers, 1921-28 (Box 34, Folder 717)
    - William Booth, 1924-28 (Box 34, Folder 718)
    - J. G. Boots, 1926 (Box 34, Folder 719)
    - Boston City Hospital, 1919-27 (Box 34, Folder 720)
    - Boston Lying-In Hospital, 1922-27 (Box 34, Folder 721)
    - Boston Psychopathic Hospital, 1923-24 (Box 34, Folder 722)
    - Boston University, 1922-24 (Box 34, Folder 723)
    - J. G. Bowman, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 724)
    - R. H. M. Bowman, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 725)
    - H. W. Boyd, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 726)
    - A. L. Boulware, 1921-25 (Box 34, Folder 727)
    - Eliott Brackett, 1921-23 (Box 34, Folder 728)
    - James Bradley, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 729)
    - Mrs. Leverett Bradley, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 730)
    - J. R. B. Branch, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 731)
    - Emilie Bretthauer, 1923-27 (Box 34, Folder 732)
    - Bridgeport Hospital, 1923-25 (Box 34, Folder 733)
    - British Chamber of Commerce, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 734)
    - British Charitable Hospital, 1921-26 (Box 34, Folder 735)
    - Adelaide Brown, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 736)
    - Douglas Bryan Brown, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 737)
    - Emma Brown, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 738)
    - N. W. Brown, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 739)
    - William A. Brown, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 740)
    - W. T. Brown, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 741)
    - Brown University, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 742)
    - O. G. Brubaker, 1919-20 (Box 34, Folder 743)
    - W. Brungate, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 744)
    - Bubonic Plague, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 745)
    - Budgets, 1919-25 (Box 34, Folder 746)
    - Budgets, 1926-28 (Box 35, Folder 747)
    - Budgets, 1926-28 (Box 35, Folder 748)
    - C. G. Bull, 1921-22 (Box 35, Folder 749)
    - Bulletin, 1921-24 (Box 35, Folder 750)
    - R. T. Burge, 1919 (Box 35, Folder 751)
    - G. R. Burke, 1925 (Box 35, Folder 752)
    - C. C. Burlingame, 1923-27 (Box 35, Folder 753)
    - Burton-Chamberlin Commission (Box 35, Folder 754)
    - Pastor Busch, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 755)
    - J. D. Bush, 1921 (Box 35, Folder 756)
    - Butterfield & Squire, 1923-24 (Box 35, Folder 757)
    - Caroline Buttrick, 1927 (Box 35, Folder 758)
    - Wallace Buttrick, 1919-26 (Box 35, Folder 759)
    - Cables, 1919-28 (Box 35, Folder 760)
    - Cables, 1919-28 (Box 35, Folder 761)
    - Cables, 1919-28 (Box 35, Folder 762)
    - Cables, 1919-28 (Box 35, Folder 763)
    - Cables, 1919-28 (Box 35, Folder 764)
    - Cables, 1919-28 (Box 35, Folder 765)
    - Cable Code, 1921-24 (Box 35, Folder 766)
    - Lyman V. Cady, 1923 (Box 35, Folder 767)
    - C. N. Caldwell, 1919 (Box 35, Folder 768)
    - Otis W. Caldwell, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 769)
    - California State Board of Health, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 770)
    - E. B. Callahan, 1920 (Box 35, Folder 771)
    - Canadian Academy, 1927 (Box 35, Folder 772)
    - Canadian Methodist Mission, 1925 (Box 35, Folder 773)
    - Canadian Prime Minister, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 774)
    - W. B. Cannon, 1919-22 (Box 35, Folder 775)
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 776)
      Political situation, labor problems, boycott, anti-Christian movement. William W. Cadbury
      Related Archival Materials note
      See also Lingnan University.
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 777)
      See also Lingnan University. Political situation, labor problems, boycott, anti-Christian movement. William W. Cadbury
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 778)
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 779)
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 780)
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 781)
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 782)
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 783)
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 784)
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 785)
    - Canton Christian College, 1919-26 (Box 36, Folder 786)
    - Canton Christian College, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 787)
    - Canton Hospital, 1919-28 (Box 37, Folder 788)
      Hospital policy, hookworm
    - Canton Hospital, 1919-28 (Box 37, Folder 789)
    - Canton Hospital, 1919-28 (Box 37, Folder 790)
    - Carbon Tetrachloride, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 791)
    - Mary E. Carleton, 1919 (Box 37, Folder 792)
    - Carleton College, 1922-24 (Box 37, Folder 793)
    - Carnegie Corporation, 1926 (Box 37, Folder 794)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1924-25 (Box 37, Folder 795)
    - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1926 (Box 37, Folder 796)
    - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 797)
    - W. B. Carpenter, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 798)
    - Mary Carter, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 799)
    - W. S. Carter, 1923-28 (Box 37, Folder 800)
    - Frank Cartwright, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 801)
    - Catholic Church, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 802)
    - Catholic Hospital Association, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 803)
    - Central China University, 1923-27 (Box 37, Folder 804)
    - Central Epidemic Prevention Bureau, 1922-28 (Box 37, Folder 805)
      Equipment, serum laboratory, government
    - Central Epidemic Prevention Bureau, 1922-28 (Box 37, Folder 806)
    - Central Hospital, 1919-28 (Box 37, Folder 807)
      Government isolation hospital, affiliation with Central Epidemic Prevention Bureau.
    - Central Hospital, 1919-28 (Box 37, Folder 808)
    - Central National University, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 809)
    - L. Y. Chu, 1926-27 (Box 37, Folder 810)
    - Q. H. Chan, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 811)
    - Charles Chandler, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 812)
    - Dr. Chandrasekharniya, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 813)
    - H. H. Chang, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 814)
    - H. P. Chang, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 815)
    - P. Y. Chang, 1919-22 (Box 37, Folder 816)
    - Sarah Chang, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 817)
    - W. C. Chang, 1919 (Box 37, Folder 818)
    - Changsha Museum, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 819)
    - C. L. Chao, 1926-27 (Box 38, Folder 820)
    - Frank E. Chapman, 1927 (Box 38, Folder 821)
    - Leo Chee, 1922 (Box 38, Folder 822)
    - Chemical Foundation, 1923-24 (Box 38, Folder 823)
    - Chemical Society of China, 1926 (Box 38, Folder 824)
    - K. H. Chen, 1920 (Box 38, Folder 825)
    - Eugene Chen, 1927 (Box 38, Folder 826)
    - L. H. Chen, 1927 (Box 38, Folder 827)
    - Pen Chen, 1922 (Box 38, Folder 828)
    - S. P. Chen, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 829)
    - Chester Hospital, 1922 (Box 38, Folder 830)
    - S. F. Chiang, 1923-27 (Box 38, Folder 831)
    - Chicago Department of Health, 1924-26 (Box 38, Folder 832)
    - Chicago Lying-In Hospital, 1919-22 (Box 38, Folder 833)
    - Chihli Fisheries School, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 834)
    - Child Labor, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 835)
      China Society resolution, Y. W. C. A., factories of Shanghai
    - Child Welfare Association of China, 1927-28 (Box 38, Folder 836)
    - S. C. Chin, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 837)
    - China, 1926-27 (Box 38, Folder 838)
    - China Commerce Club, 1919 (Box 38, Folder 839)
    - China Continuation Committee, 1919-20 (Box 38, Folder 840)
    - China Christian Educational Association, 1919-28 (Box 38, Folder 841)
    - China Foundation for the Promotion of Education and Culture, June 1926-28 (Box 38, Folder 842)
      Promotion of scientific education; general education; supervise the disbursement of the American Boxer Indemnity.
    - China Foundation for the Promotion of Education and Culture, June 1926-28 (Box 38, Folder 843)
    - China Foundation for the Promotion of Education and Culture, June 1926-28 (Box 38, Folder 844)
    - China Foundation for the Promotion of Education and Culture, June 1926-28 (Box 38, Folder 845)
    - China Foundation for the Promotion of Education and Culture, June 1926-28 (Box 38, Folder 846)
    - China Inland Mission, 1921-26 (Box 38, Folder 847)
    - China Institute, 1926-28 (Box 38, Folder 848)
    - China International Famine Policy Commission, 1922-27 (Box 38, Folder 849)
    - China Medical Association, 1927-28 (Box 39, Folder 850)
    - China Medical Board, 1920-23 (Box 39, Folder 851)
    - China Medical Boat Fund, 1924-26 (Box 39, Folder 852)
    - China Ministry of Education, 1924-27 (Box 39, Folder 853)
    - China Ministry of Foreign Affairs, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 854)
    - China Mission Yearbook, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 855)
    - China National Amateur Athletic Association, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 856)
    - China Society of America, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 857)
    - China Medical Journal, 1919-26 (Box 39, Folder 858)
    - China Medical Missionary Association, 1919-26 (Box 39, Folder 859)
      Medical literature and translation, see also China Medical Association.
    - China Medical Missionary Association, 1919-26 (Box 39, Folder 860)
    - China Medical Missionary Association, 1919-26 (Box 39, Folder 861)
    - China Medical Missionary Association, 1919-26 (Box 39, Folder 862)
    - China Medical Missionary Association, 1919-26 (Box 39, Folder 863)
    - China Society for America, 1921-25 (Box 39, Folder 864)
    - China Union University (Box 39, Folder 865)
    - China Weekly Review, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 866)
    - Chinese Christian Education Association, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 867)
    - Chinese Christian Union, 1925-26 (Box 39, Folder 868)
    - Chinese Commission, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 869)
    - Chinese Consul, 1919-21 (Box 39, Folder 870)
    - Chinese Eastern Railway, 1928 (Box 39, Folder 871)
    - Chinese Educational Commission, 1919-24 (Box 39, Folder 872)
    - Chinese Educational Reform Association, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 873)
    - Chinese Employees, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 874)
    - Chinese Geological Survey, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 875)
    - Chinese Hospital, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 876)
      San Francisco
    - Chinese Journal of Physiology, 1927-28 (Box 40, Folder 877)
    - Chinese Legation, 1921-27 (Box 40, Folder 878)
    - Chinese Medical Commission, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 879)
    - Chinese Medical Students, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 880)
    - Chinese Names, 1919-20 (Box 40, Folder 881)
    - Chinese National Welfare Society, 1919 (Box 40, Folder 882)
    - Chinese Physiological Society, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 883)
    - Chinese Red Cross Society, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 884)
    - Chinese Republic, 1919 (Box 40, Folder 885)
    - Chinese Social and Political Science Association Library, 1922-27 (Box 40, Folder 886)
    - Chinese Students Aid, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 887)
    - Chinese Students Alliance, 1919-26 (Box 40, Folder 888)
    - Chinese Students Christian Alliance, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 889)
    - Chinese Students Club, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 890)
    - Chinese Students in America, 1919-27 (Box 40, Folder 891)
      Health
    - Chinese Students Monthly, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 892)
    - Sarah Ching, 1919 (Box 40, Folder 893)
    - Chosen Christian College, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 894)
    - Y. C. Chow, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 895)
    - C. C. Choyce, 1922-24 (Box 40, Folder 896)
    - Christian Colleges in China, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 897)
    - Christian Education, 1923-29 (Box 40, Folder 898)
    - Christian Herald, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 899)
    - Christian Reformed Church of America, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 900)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1919 (Box 40, Folder 901)
    - C. T. Chu, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 902)
    - T. C. Chu, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 903)
    - Walter Chu, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 904)
    - Annie Chung, 1920-22 (Box 40, Folder 905)
    - Chung Wha University, 1924-25 (Box 40, Folder 906)
    - Chung Shan University, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 907)
    - Chungking, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 908)
    - Church of the Brethren, 1919-25 (Box 40, Folder 909)
    - Church of the Brethren Mission Hospital - Pintingchow, 1919-24 (Box 40, Folder 910)
    - Church Missionary Society, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 911)
    - Church of Scotland, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 912)
    - Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Ichang, 1919-28 (Box 40, Folder 913)
    - Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Ichang, 1919-28 (Box 40, Folder 914)
    - Cincinatti General Hospital, 1921-27 (Box 41, Folder 915)
    - Sidney Clark, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 916)
    - Cleanliness Institute, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 917)
    - H. L. Clift, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 918)
    - W. R. Coe, 1919-22 (Box 41, Folder 919)
    - College of the City of New York, 1919-24 (Box 41, Folder 920)
    - College Entrance Examination Board, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 921)
    - College of Physicians and Surgeons, 1919-24 (Box 41, Folder 922)
    - Columbia University, 1919-28 (Box 41, Folder 923)
      Education surveys, Chinese education
    - Columbia University, 1919-28 (Box 41, Folder 924)
    - Columbia University, 1919-28 (Box 41, Folder 925)
    - Commercial Press Limited, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 926)
    - Commission of Chinese Medical Scientists, 1922-23 (Box 41, Folder 927)
      To travel in the United States.
    - Committee on Christian Education in China, 1920-21 (Box 41, Folder 928)
    - Committee on Dispensary Development, 1920-27 (Box 41, Folder 929)
    - Committee on Educational Research, 1921-22 (Box 41, Folder 930)
    - Committee on Reference & Council of Foreign Mission Conference of North America, 1919-28 (Box 41, Folder 931)
    - Committee on Reference & Council of Foreign Mission Conference of North America, 1919-28 (Box 41, Folder 932)
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1922-25 (Box 41, Folder 933)
    - Comptroller, 1920-23 (Box 41, Folder 934)
    - Conference on American Relations with China, 1925-26 (Box 41, Folder 935)
    - Conference on Far East Affairs, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 936)
    - Lewis A. Conner, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 937)
    - Constantinople Women's College, 1922 (Box 41, Folder 938)
    - (Folder does not exist) (Box 41, Folder 939)
    - Contracts, 1919 (Box 41, Folder 940)
    - Cook County Hospital, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 941)
    - Charles Coolidge, 1923-25 (Box 42, Folder 942)
    - James Cooper, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 943)
    - Cooperation Among Missions, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 944)
    - Cooperative Campaign Work, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 945)
    - Oliver Cope, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 946)
    - Copp Hospital, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 947)
    - James J. Corbett, 1923 (Box 42, Folder 948)
    - Corn Exchange Bank, 1925-26 (Box 42, Folder 949)
    - Cornell Clinic, 1922-26 (Box 42, Folder 950)
    - Cornell College, 1923 (Box 42, Folder 951)
    - Cornell University, 1920-28 (Box 42, Folder 952)
    - Charles W. Coulter, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 953)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1924-27 (Box 42, Folder 954)
    - Council on Health Education, 1920-28 (Box 42, Folder 955)
      Public Health; W. W. Peter
    - Council on Health Education, 1920-28 (Box 42, Folder 956)
    - Council on Health Education, 1920-28 (Box 42, Folder 957)
    - Council on Health Education, 1920-28 (Box 42, Folder 958)
    - Council on Health Education, 1920-28 (Box 42, Folder 959)
    - Council on Health Education - Posters (Box 42, Folder 960)
    - Council on Higher Education, 1925-28 (Box 42, Folder 961)
    - Council on Public Health, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 962)
    - W. T. Councilman, 1926-27 (Box 42, Folder 963)
    - James R. Cox, 1922-25 (Box 42, Folder 964)
    - Helen F. Craig, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 965)
    - Grace Crandall, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 966)
    - Charles R. Crane, 1921-27 (Box 43, Folder 967)
    - Helen B. Crane, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 968)
    - L. F. Carver, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 969)
    - A. N. Creadick, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 970)
    - Crematorium, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 971)
    - A. J. Crockford, 1922-24 (Box 43, Folder 972)
    - Bowman C. Crowell, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 973)
    - T. S. Cullen, 1919-21 (Box 43, Folder 974)
    - W. R. Cunningham, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 975)
    - John Curtin, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 976)
    - Daily Vacation Bible Schools, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 977)
    - Darien Marine Products Station, 1923-24 (Box 43, Folder 978)
    - S. Darling, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 979)
    - John W. Davis, 1922-26 (Box 43, Folder 980)
    - Katherine Bement Davis, 1919-23 (Box 43, Folder 981)
    - G. Glass Davit, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 982)
    - Thomas M. Debevoise, 1924-27 (Box 43, Folder 983)
    - Decatur and Mason County Hospital, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 984)
    - Decorations, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 985)
    - Jacob De Hass, 1926-27 (Box 43, Folder 986)
    - Mrs. Louis De Lamarter, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 987)
    - Dennison University, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 988)
    - William C. Dennis, 1923-24 (Box 43, Folder 989)
    - Dental Education, 1921-24 (Box 43, Folder 990)
    - Denver University, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 991)
    - D. W. Deshler, 1922-23 (Box 43, Folder 992)
    - Albert Dewey, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 993)
    - John Dewey, 1921-24 (Box 43, Folder 994)
    - Elsie Dexter, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 995)
    - Robert L. Dickinson, 1919-25 (Box 43, Folder 996)
    - E. J. M. Dickson, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 997)
    - Director - Roger S. Greene, 1921-25 (Box 43, Folder 998)
      General; Cross References
    - Director - Roger S. Greene, 1921-25 (Box 43, Folder 999)
    - Director - Roger S. Greene, 1921-25 (Box 43, Folder 1000)
    - Director - Roger S. Greene, 1921-25 (Box 43, Folder 1001)
    - Director - Roger S. Greene, 1921-25 (Box 43, Folder 1002)
    - O. C. Doeruy, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 1003)
    - Dormitories, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 1004)
    - John Downey, 1919-23 (Box 43, Folder 1005)
    - Anna Drake, 1924-25 (Box 43, Folder 1006)
    - George Draper, 1924-25 (Box 43, Folder 1007)
    - Anna Dreyful, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 1008)
    - Cecil K. Drinket, 1920-24 (Box 43, Folder 1009)
    - E. C. Dudley, 1920 (Box 44, Folder 1010)
    - Mrs. Balfour Duffus, 1926 (Box 44, Folder 1011)
    - Duke University, 1927 (Box 44, Folder 1012)
    - E. J. Dukes, 1922 (Box 44, Folder 1013)
    - Mrs. Allen W. Dulles, 1926 (Box 44, Folder 1014)
    - East China Christian Education Association, 1923-28 (Box 44, Folder 1015)
    - Education in China, 1919-28 (Box 44, Folder 1016)
    - Education in China, 1919-28 (Box 44, Folder 1017)
    - Educational Institutions in China, 1925-26 (Box 44, Folder 1018)
    - Martin Egan, 1921 (Box 44, Folder 1019)
    - Margery K. Eggleston, 1920-27 (Box 44, Folder 1020)
    - Marie Elliott, 1921 (Box 44, Folder 1021)
    - G. M. Ellis, 1922-26 (Box 44, Folder 1022)
    - Edwin R. Embree, 1919-26 (Box 44, Folder 1023)
    - Edwin R. Embree, 1919-26 (Box 44, Folder 1024)
    - Emergency Fund, 1921-28 (Box 44, Folder 1025)
      Protection of personnel, equipment
    - Frederick Endler, 1924-25 (Box 44, Folder 1026)
    - Engineering School, 1921 (Box 44, Folder 1027)
    - Engineering Society, 1926 (Box 44, Folder 1028)
    - Ensworth Methodist Hospital, 1922 (Box 44, Folder 1029)
    - Rutger Essen, 1920 (Box 44, Folder 1030)
    - William Ellinger, 1920 (Box 44, Folder 1031)
    - M. D. Eubank, 1922-24 (Box 44, Folder 1032)
    - Evangelical Lutheran Augustana Synod, 1922-24 (Box 44, Folder 1033)
    - Edward Evans, 1920 (Box 44, Folder 1034)
    - Exchange Rates and Aggreements with Mission Boards, 1918-19 (Box 44, Folder 1035)
    - Exchange, 1920-26 (Box 45, Folder 1036)
    - Exchange, 1920-26 (Box 45, Folder 1037)
    - Exchange, 1920-26 (Box 45, Folder 1038)
    - Exchange, 1920-26 (Box 45, Folder 1039)
    - Famine Relief, 1920-28 (Box 45, Folder 1040)
      Nanking and Peking Floods, Hwai River Basin, dike construction, drainage, sanitary work
    - Famine Relief, 1920-28 (Box 45, Folder 1041)
    - Famine Relief, 1920-28 (Box 45, Folder 1042)
    - Famine Relief, 1920-28 (Box 45, Folder 1043)
    - Fan Memorial Biological Survey, 1928 (Box 45, Folder 1044)
    - Far Eastern Association of Tropical Medicine, 1925 (Box 45, Folder 1045)
    - Far Eastern Review, 1919-20 (Box 45, Folder 1046)
    - Max Farrand, 1921 (Box 45, Folder 1047)
    - Federal Council of Churches, 1920-28 (Box 45, Folder 1048)
    - Fellowship - Sheonan Cheer, 1919-22 (Box 45, Folder 1049)
    - Fellowship - H. P. Chu, 1919 (Box 45, Folder 1050)
    - Fellowship - Shih Ying Chu, 1921-23 (Box 45, Folder 1051)
    - Fellowship - Anna Haaland, 1920-21 (Box 45, Folder 1052)
    - Fellowship - Chen Hsiang Hu, 1919-21 (Box 45, Folder 1053)
    - Fellowship - Yu Hua Kao, 1923-24 (Box 45, Folder 1054)
    - Fellowship - Yu Hua Kao, 1923-24 (Box 45, Folder 1055)
    - Fellowship - Edward Y. Kau, 1919-20 (Box 45, Folder 1056)
    - Fellowship - Tse King, 1919-20 (Box 46, Folder 1057)
    - Fellowship - Blanche Li, 1923-24 (Box 46, Folder 1058)
    - Fellowship - Blanche Li, 1923-24 (Box 46, Folder 1059)
    - Fellowship - K. H. Li, 1920-21 (Box 46, Folder 1060)
    - Fellowship - Chong Eang Lim, 1919-22 (Box 46, Folder 1061)
    - Fellowship - Ven Tsas Loh, 1919-20 (Box 46, Folder 1062)
    - Fellowship - Wen Chao Mu, 1920 (Box 46, Folder 1063)
    - Fellowship - P. L. McAll, 1919 (Box 46, Folder 1064)
    - Fellowship - Cheuk Sang Mei, 1919-20 (Box 46, Folder 1065)
    - Fellowship - Lee M. Miles, 1920-21 (Box 46, Folder 1066)
    - Fellowship - W. S. Thacker-Neville, 1919 (Box 46, Folder 1067)
    - Fellowship - Mary Tai, 1919-21 (Box 46, Folder 1068)
    - Fellowship - Zingling Tai, 1919-21 (Box 46, Folder 1069)
    - Fellowship - Hugh Taylor, 1922 (Box 46, Folder 1070)
    - Fellowship - S. D. Tsiang, 1919-22 (Box 46, Folder 1071)
    - Fellowship - Long Teh (Ernest) Tso, 1919-20 (Box 46, Folder 1072)
    - Fellowship - Marguerite Warfield, 1920-21 (Box 47, Folder 1073)
    - Fellowship - L. S. Woo, 1919-20 (Box 47, Folder 1074)
    - Fellowship - Loo Sung Woo, 1919 (Box 47, Folder 1075)
    - Fellowship - S. T. Woo, 1919-23 (Box 47, Folder 1076)
    - Fellowship - Fuchun Yen, 1921-22 (Box 47, Folder 1077)
    - Fellowship - Wei Li Yih, 1919 (Box 47, Folder 1078)
    - Fellowship - Sung Dan Zau, 1919-20 (Box 47, Folder 1079)
    - Fellowships, 1918-20 (Box 47, Folder 1080)
    - Fellowships - General, 1920-24 (Box 47, Folder 1081)
      Policy, some individual comment, statistics, NRC-RF medical fellowships
    - Fellowships - General, 1920-24 (Box 47, Folder 1082)
    - Fellowships - General, 1920-24 (Box 47, Folder 1083)
    - Fellowships - General, 1920-24 (Box 47, Folder 1084)
    - Fellowships - General, 1920-24 (Box 47, Folder 1085)
    - Fellowships - General, 1925-28 (Box 48, Folder 1086)
    - Fellowships - General, 1925-28 (Box 48, Folder 1087)
    - Fellowships - General, 1925-28 (Box 48, Folder 1088)
    - Fellowships - General, 1925-28 (Box 48, Folder 1089)
    - Fellowships - General, 1925-28 (Box 48, Folder 1090)
    - Fellowships - General, 1925-28 (Box 48, Folder 1091)
    - Fellowships - General, 1925-28 (Box 48, Folder 1092)
    - Fellowships - Nurses, 1923 (Box 48, Folder 1093)